Guide to the Doris Duke Papers, 1798-2003 and undated (bulk 1930-1999)
Duke University. University Archives
- Reports and Summaries, 1930-1996 and undated
  - Inventory Cards, circa 1930s-1990s and undated
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Playhouse, circa 1970s-1990s (1 of 5) (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Playhouse, circa 1970s-1990s (2 of 5) (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Playhouse, circa 1970s-1990s (3 of 5) (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Playhouse, circa 1970s-1990s (4 of 5) (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Playhouse, circa 1970s-1990s (5 of 5) (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Miss Duke's Bedroom, circa 1970s-1990s (1 of 6) (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Miss Duke's Bedroom, circa 1970s-1990s (2 of 6) (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Miss Duke's Bedroom, circa 1970s-1990s (3 of 6) (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Miss Duke's Bedroom, circa 1970s-1990s (4 of 6) (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Miss Duke's Bedroom, circa 1970s-1990s (5 of 6) (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Miss Duke's Bedroom, circa 1970s-1990s (6 of 6) (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Living Room, circa 1970s-1990s (1 of 4) (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Living Room, circa 1970s-1990s (2 of 4) (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Living Room, circa 1970s-1990s (3 of 4) (Box 232, Folder 3)
    - Inventory Cards, Shangri La - Living Room, circa 1970s-1990s (4 of 4) (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - Invoices and correspondence regarding goods shipped by Thomas Cook & Son, 1935-1939 (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Invoices (copies & originals) from art/antique dealers for art, furniture, and objects purchased from 1930s-1960s. Arranged alphabetically by vendor, 1935-1969 (1 of 4) (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Invoices (copies & originals) from art/antique dealers for art, furniture, and objects purchased from 1930s-1960s. Arranged alphabetically by vendor, 1935-1969 (2 of 4) (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Invoices (copies & originals) from art/antique dealers for art, furniture, and objects purchased from 1930s-1960s. Arranged alphabetically by vendor, 1935-1969 (3 of 4) (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Invoices (copies & originals) from art/antique dealers for art, furniture, and objects purchased from 1930s-1960s. Arranged alphabetically by vendor, 1935-1969 (4 of 4) (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence from Steuben Glass regarding antique glass, 1941 Nov 1 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Inventory reference - Duke Gardens, 1959-1970 (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - Inventory Somerville - Basement, 1964-1973 (Box 233, Folder 8)
    - Inventory reference - decorating, 1968-1970 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Somerville Inventory - EMC pending, 1968-1972 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Medical Supplies Inventory, 1974 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Honolulu Wine Inventory, 1976 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Fabric Samples - Newport (Rough Point), undated (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - Furniture list to be brought from Beverly Hills to Somerville, undated (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Historical Society, undated (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - Inventory, Duke Farms - Butlers Pantry, undated (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - Items loaned or donated to Duke Gardens Foundation, undated (Box 234, Folder 9)
- Subject Files, 1905-2004 and undated
  The Subject Files series reflect the categories either Miss Duke or her staff established to organize her personal and professional records. This series contains a wide assortment of materials ranging from financial records to scrapbooks created by Doris Duke when she was a child. The series is further arranged into twenty one subseries.
  RESTRICTED: Access to folders in boxes 242, 256, 257, 291, 294, 296, 303, and 332 are restricted and require prior written approval from the Doris Duke Charitable Foundation to view.
  - Airplanes, 1947-1999 (bulk 1987-1996)
    Doris Duke's Boeing 737-300 airplane was placed into service in 1987 and was sold in January 1995 after her death. The materials document the refurbishing, repairs and maintenance, and personal use of the aircraft. Materials include invoices, correspondence, manuals, fueling cards, reports, passenger manifests, insurance on the aircraft, applications for licensing of facilities, and travel itineraries and associated costs to different locations both in the United States and abroad.
    Arrangement Note: This subseries has been left in the original order it was found and presumably created in. For the most part, this subseries is arranged alphabetically and chronologically thereunder.
    - Correspondence and memoranda to Irwin Bloom relating to a variety of issues involving Doris Duke’s airplane. Topics include keys to aviation office and resignation of a mechanic, 1989 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence and memoranda regarding the administration and operation of Doris Duke's Boeing 737, 1993-1994 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, and related materials concerning maintenance schedules, inventory, aviation badges, and credit cards for Doris Duke's Boeing 737, 1991-1998 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda, copies of articles, and related materials concerning aviation information, 1989-1992 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence relating to Duke Farms Agreements with the Federal Aviation Administration (FAA), 1988 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, memoranda and other materials concerning a variety of topics including requirements by HI to use state airports, plane inspections of upgrades to interior, and charges for work, 1989-1990 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence between Duke Farms and the Dee Howard Company regarding the interior design of Doris Duke’s Boeing 737. Includes inventory of food, bedding, maintenance items, etc. on board plane, 1989-1990 (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - Passenger manifest for trip to Morristown from Geneva, 1991 (Box 235, Folder 8)
    - Map of a proposed Solberg Jetport, undated (Box 235, Folder 9)
    - Instruction manual, Electronic Data Retrieval System, Universal Weather and Aviation, 1988-1989 (Box 235, Folder 10)
    - Invoices for repairs and maintenance performed on the Boeing 737 by Aeroflight. Includes a manual for flight crew procedures aboard Duke Farms Inc. Boeing 737, 1991-1995 (Box 235, Folder 11)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Aeronautical Radio, Inc., 1988-1991 (Box 235, Folder 12)
    - Invoices for services rendered by AerRianta Cork, 1991 (Box 235, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and memoranda Airplane brokerage, from those interested in purchasing Doris Duke’s 737 plane if she is ever interested in selling, 1990-1992 (Box 235, Folder 14)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Air Treads and associated vendors, 1993–1994 (Box 235, Folder 15)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Allied Signal, Inc., such as refueling the Boeing 737 as well as renting hangar space to store the airplane, 1988-1994 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Aloha Airlines, 1987–1989 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Monthly account statement for Doris Duke's American Express card, 1988 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Invoices for services rendered by America West Airlines, 1989-1990 (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Invoices for services rendered by America West Airlines, 1991-1994 (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Angus Trent, 1988 (Box 236, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Apeiron Technology, 1992 (Box 236, Folder 7)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Arinc, 1992–1995 (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Arthur Rothlein Agency, Inc., 1988 (Box 236, Folder 9)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Asrainbow/Leisure Air Limited, 1988 (Box 236, Folder 10)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Associated Air Center, 1991–1995 (Box 236, Folder 11)
    - Automatic Data Processing (ADP) payroll forms, 1988–1989 (Box 236, Folder 12)
    - Invoices regarding repairs and maintenance work performed on the Boeing 737. Includes memoranda regarding the selling of the airplane and the closing of accounts, 1993-1995 (Box 236, Folder 13)
    - Invoices for repair and maintenance work performed on the Boeing 737 by Aviall, 1993-1996 (Box 236, Folder 14)
    - Invoices for reimbursements made to Doris Duke’s account at the Bank of Hawaii, 1988 (Box 236, Folder 15)
    - Invoices for a portable photocopier purchased at Bi-Rite, 1988 (Box 236, Folder 16)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Boeing Commercial Airplane Group, 1987–1990 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Boeing Commercial Airplane Group, 1991 (Box 237, Folder 2)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Boeing Commercial Airplane Group, 1992–1995 (Box 237, Folder 3)
    - Invoices for landing at Burbank-Glendale-Pasadena Airport Authority, 1991 (Box 237, Folder 4)
    - Invoices for freight shipments Burlington Air Express, 1991 (Box 237, Folder 5)
    - Invoices for modifications to Doris Duke's Boeing 737 by Carrier Aircraft Interiors. Includes color photographs, 1991-1993 (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Century Aviation, 1991–1992 (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - Bank statements, Chemical Bank account, 1989 (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - Bank statements, Chemical Bank account, 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 237, Folder 9)
    - Bank statements, Chemical Bank account, 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 237, Folder 10)
    - Bank statements, Chemical Bank account, 1991-1992 (Box 237, Folder 11)
    - Bank statements and ledgers, Chemical Bank account, 1991-1992 (1 of 3) (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Bank statements and ledgers, Chemical Bank account, 1991-1992 (2 of 3) (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Bank statements and ledgers, Chemical Bank account, 1991-1992 (3 of 3) (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Monthly statement for charges made on Doris Duke’s Chemlink Express account, 1993 (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - Invoices for services rendered by the Civilian Aviation Authority, 1991-1992 (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Clay Lacy Aviation, 1991–1994 (1 of 2) (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Clay Lacy Aviation, 1991–1994 (2 of 2) (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, and related materials concerning publications in the Aviation Office shipped to Colm Kennedy Aircraft Services and proposal discussions about interior design of plane (C. Heffner letter), 1988-1992 (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - Invoices and related materials concerning flight arrangements for Doris Duke’s Boeing 737. Includes copy of License Certificate for the Duke Farms Heliport (private use), 1989-1991 (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - Completed scheduled maintenance, 1987 (Box 238, Folder 10)
    - Flight log reports, 1987-1988 (Box 238, Folder 11)
    - Maintenance log reports, 1987-1988 (Box 238, Folder 12)
    - Invoices and correspondence related to services for Boeing 737, 1988 (Box 238, Folder 13)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1989-1990 (1 of 3) (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1989-1990 (2 of 3) (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1989-1990 (3 of 3) (Box 239, Folder 3)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1991 Jan-Jun (Box 239, Folder 4)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1991 Jul-Dec (1 of 2) (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1991 Jul-Dec (2 of 2) (Box 239, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1992 (1 of 2) (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1992 (2 of 2) (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - Invoices and requests for reimbursements from Colm Kennedy Airport Services to Doris Duke, 1992 (1 of 2) (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - Invoices and requests for reimbursements from Colm Kennedy Airport Services to Doris Duke, 1992 (2 of 2) (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - Fax transmissions from Colm Kennedy to Bernard Lafferty regarding plane destinations, 1993 (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1993 (1 of 2) (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1993 (2 of 2) (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1994-1995 (2 of 2) (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Colm Kennedy Airport Services, 1994-1995 (2 of 2) (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - Invoices for Columbia Lumber purchases for Doris Duke’s airplane, 1994 (Box 241, Folder 3)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Cosgrove Aircraft Service, 1988 (Box 241, Folder 4)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Crowe and Dunlevy, 1987 (Box 241, Folder 5)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Daniel Systems, 1987-1994 (Box 241, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Dee Howard Company, 1989-1990 (Box 241, Folder 7)
    - Petty cash reconciliation sheets, Duke Business Office, 1988-1989 (Box 241, Folder 8)
    - Balance statements, Duke Farms, Inc., 1988–1990 (Box 241, Folder 9)
    - Invoices and memoranda for services rendered to Duke Farms, Inc., 1991-1994 (Box 241, Folder 10)
    - Check request for wrestling mats to aid in transportation of camels ordered from Effinger’s, 1988 (Box 241, Folder 11)
    - Invoices and payroll statements for services rendered by Captain Ernest J. Betz in relation to Doris Duke’s Boeing 737, 1988 (Box 241, Folder 12)
    - Invoices from Eurocontrol for services rendered, 1991-1993 (Box 241, Folder 13)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Exclusive Protection, 1987 (Box 241, Folder 14)
    - Credit card receipts for services rendered by Exxon, 1987-1993 (Box 241, Folder 15)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Fast Print, 1988 (Box 241, Folder 16)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Federal Express, 1988-1990 (Box 241, Folder 17)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Federal Express, 1991-1994 (Box 241, Folder 18)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Flightpath Services, 1992 (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Forms Plus, 1993 (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Receipts for reimbursements for Captain George Abdul for his service as pilot for Doris Duke, 1987-1988 (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - Check and memoranda, Hawaii State Tax Collector, 1988 (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Insured Aircraft Title Service, Inc., 1987 (Box 242, Folder 5)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Irwin E. Bloom, Duke Farms Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 242, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Jeppesen Sanderson, 1991-1995 (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - Airplane Specifications, undated (1 of 2) (Box 242, Folder 8)
    - Airplane Specifications, undated (2 of 2) (Box 242, Folder 9)
    - Fabric samples for airplane, 1991 (Box 242, Folder 10)
    - Resignation letter of pilot Ken DeWitt, sent to Chandi Heffner (copy), 1989 Oct 12 (Box 242, Folder 11)
    - Invoices, memoranda, meeting minutes, and notes pertaining to services rendered by Jet Aviation, 1986–1988 (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Jet Aviation, 1988-1990 (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - Invoices sent to Doris Duke from Jet Aviation for trips taken by Doris Duke aboard chartered planes, 1991 (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Jet Aviation, 1991-1992 (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - Memoranda regarding Duke Farms, Inc. account with Jet Aviation, 1994-1996 (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - Invoices and receipts for services rendered by Kenneth J. DeWitt, 1988 (1 of 2) (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - Invoices and receipts for services rendered by Kenneth J. DeWitt, 1988 (2 of 2) (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - Invoices and receipts for services rendered by Kenneth J. DeWitt, 1988-1989 (1 of 2) (Box 243, Folder 8)
    - Invoices and receipts for services rendered by Kenneth J. DeWitt, 1988-1989 (2 of 2) (Box 243, Folder 9)
    - Invoices for services rendered by KSH Group, Inc. Insurance, 1987-1990 (Box 244, Folder 1)
    - Invoices and memoranda for a policy held with KSH Group, Inc. Insurance, 1991-1994 (Box 244, Folder 2)
    - Invoices and receipts for services rendered by McDonald Aviation Services, 1988 (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - Invoices for legal services rendered by Martin Zinman, 1992-1993 (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Motorola, 1988–1989 (1 of 2) (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Motorola, 1988–1989 (2 of 2) (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Motorola, 1991 (Box 244, Folder 7)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Multi Service, 1987-1989 (Box 244, Folder 8)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Multi Service, 1991-1995 (Box 244, Folder 9)
    - Invoices for services rendered by the New York State Department of Transportation, 1988 (Box 244, Folder 10)
    - Invoices for services rendered by PAB Aviation, 1987 (Box 244, Folder 11)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Page Avjet Corporation, 1987 (Box 244, Folder 12)
    - Invoices for services rendered by the Port Authority of N.Y. and N.J., 1992-1994 (Box 244, Folder 13)
    - Invoices for services rendered by the Republic of the Philippines, Department of Transportation and Communications, 1992 (Box 244, Folder 14)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Robinson, Wayne, Levin, Riccio, and La Sala, attorneys-at-law, 1988–1990 (Box 244, Folder 15)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Rockwell International, 1991-1994 (Box 244, Folder 16)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Ryder Airline Services, 1993 (Box 244, Folder 17)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Scandia Down Shops, 1988 (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Shanahan's, 1988 (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - Sales brochure for a Boeing 737-300 issued by Smith/Ellis, Professional Brokerage of Business Jets, 1987 (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Somerset Press, 1988 (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - Check receipt, State of New Jersey, 1988 (Box 245, Folder 5)
    - Invoices for services rendered by United Airlines, 1991-1995 (Box 245, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for services rendered by United Airlines, 1992-1995 (Box 245, Folder 7)
    - Invoices for services rendered by United Parcel Service, 1988 (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - Invoices for services rendered by United Sheetmetal, Inc., 1988 (Box 245, Folder 9)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Universal Weather and Aviation, 1987-1989 (1 of 2) (Box 245, Folder 10)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Universal Weather and Aviation, 1987-1989 (2 of 2) (Box 245, Folder 11)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Universal Weather and Aviation, 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 245, Folder 12)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Universal Weather and Aviation, 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 245, Folder 13)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Universal Weather and Aviation, 1991 (Box 245, Folder 14)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Universal Weather and Aviation, 1991-1995 (1 of 2) (Box 246, Folder 1)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Universal Weather and Aviation, 1991-1995 (2 of 2) (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Universal Weather and Aviation, 1992 (1 of 2) (Box 246, Folder 3)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Universal Weather and Aviation, 1992 (2 of 2) (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Universal Weather and Aviation, 1993 (1 of 2) (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Universal Weather and Aviation, 1993 (2 of 2) (Box 246, Folder 6)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Uvair, 1988-1994 (1 of 2) (Box 246, Folder 7)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Uvair, 1988-1994 (2 of 2) (Box 246, Folder 8)
    - Invoices, receipts, statements, and other financial materials relating to Doris Duke’s Boeing 737. Topics include furnishing the interior, hiring pilots for trips, repairs, and supplies, 1988-1990 (1 of 2) (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - Invoices, receipts, statements, and other financial materials relating to Doris Duke’s Boeing 737. Topics include furnishing the interior, hiring pilots for trips, repairs, and supplies, 1988-1990 (2 of 2) (Box 247, Folder 2)
    - Invoices for services rendered by various vendors, 1988–1992 (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Invoice for maintenance repairs made by William Goldsmith, 1988 (Box 247, Folder 4)
    - Invoices for services rendered by Yellow Freight Systems, 1988 (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - Copy of Boeing 737-300 plane registration, 1987 (Box 247, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, memoranda, and related materials concerning insurance for the Boeing 737, pilot qualifications, and materials from Southern Airlines Co. since they are providing training for all pilots employed by Duke Farms, Inc., 1988 (Box 247, Folder 7)
    - Notification of fuel permits to pick up airplane fuel in GA and FL and drive back to N.J., 1990 (Box 247, Folder 8)
    - Fair market appraisal of the Boeing 737, 1994 (Box 247, Folder 9)
    - Bill of sale, receipts, and other financial materials relating to Doris Duke’s purchase of a converted North American B-25J airplane for $75,000 in 1947. File also includes materials relating to crash near Teterboro Airport in 1948, 1947–1948 (Box 247, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda relating to helicopter arrangements for Chandi Heffner and Dr. Malpeso, 1989-1991 (Box 247, Folder 11)
    - License Certificates for Heliport at Duke Farms, 1962-1992 (Box 247, Folder 12)
  - American Indian History Project, 1961-1983
    This small collection provides some insight to the funds provided by Doris Duke (via the Doris Duke Foundation) to "develop an authentic and elaborate history of the American Indians." Materials include correspondence, newspaper clippings and progress reports as a result of the funds provided by the Doris Duke Foundation. Also included are a few research proposals for different projects as part of the American Indian History Project.
    - Correspondence to W.C. Davidson at Duke University from Harold E. Driver at Indiana University regarding writing a book about the American Indian History Project, 1961 (Box 248, Folder 1)
    - Memorandum requesting a two year extension of the American Indian History Project at the University of Utah, 1976 (Box 248, Folder 2)
    - Newspaper clippings detailing the plight and struggles of the American Indian. These clippings provide an understanding for the need for the American Indian History Project, 1962 (Box 248, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and quarterly reports on the progress of the American Indian History Project. Includes proposals for additional projects to be undertaken as a part of the American Indian History Project, 1966-1968 (1 of 2) (Box 248, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and quarterly reports on the progress of the American Indian History Project. Includes proposals for additional projects to be undertaken as a part of the American Indian History Project, 1966-1968 (2 of 2) (Box 248, Folder 5)
    - Guidelines for oral history of American Indians, undated (Box 248, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence regarding Doris Duke's continuing support of the American Indian cause, 1983 (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - The Animal Medical Center, 1966-1974